Guide to The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll 1845 - 1993 MSS 057
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 2: Manuscripts
  - Subseries 2A: Manuscripts by Charles L. Dodgson.
    - Dodgson, Charles Let q=.."" Ms, 2pp [Christ Church], [Oxford], [n.d.] (X148) Series of questions/theorems numbered with roman numerals ." 11.25 x 4.25, undated; 1706 (Box 6, Folder 471)
    - Dodgson, Charles "5329 Articles.." Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (XIX 552) A tally of sums. 8.75 x 12, undated; 1709 (Box 6, Folder 472)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Alice in Wonderland/A Dream Play/For Children" Ms, 1p [n.p.],[n.d.] (344) Title page mock up. 7.5 x 5, undated; 1710 (Box 6, Folder 473)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Arithmetical Croquet" Ms, 1p [n.p.],[n.d.] (XX 566). 7 x 9, undated; 1711 (Box 6, Folder 474)
    - Dodgson, Charles "A Charade" Mss illus, 3pp [n.p.], April 8, 1878 (332)Cyclostyle. Inscribed "B.H. from C.L.D." Signed "Lewis Carroll". (Box 6, Folder 475)
    - Dodgson, Charles "A Charade" Mss illus, 3pp [n.p.], March 31, 1890 (333)Cyclostyle. Inscribed "Presented to Edith Blakemore/by the Author - Mar. 31, 1890." Cyclostyle drawings appended and modifed by Dodgson. Signed "Lewis Carroll" 8.75 x 11.25, 1716 (Box 6, Folder 476)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Declamation Read in Hall" Ms, 4pp [n.p.], May 3, 1854 (XIX 448) 9 x 14, 1719 (Box 6, Folder 477)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Dedicated to a tea-tea. Why? Oh when?" Mss, 1p [n.p.], March 16, 1880 (III 40) Acrostic originally send to Alexandra Kitchin. Signed "Lewis Carroll". 9 x 7, 1724 (Box 6, Folder 478)
    - Dodgson, Charles "A Dream Cast" Ms, 2pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (345) Cast list for Saville-Clark play. 9 x 5.5, undated; 1725 (Box 6, Folder 479)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Formulae [Group C.]" Ms, 3pp [n.p.], March 11, 1878. 9 x 11, 1728 (Box 6, Folder 480)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Formulae [Group C.]" Ms, 3pp [n.p.], March 11, 1878 Not hand written. Printed with holograph corrections. 9 x 11, 1732 (Box 6, Folder 481)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Formulae F" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] Portion of document pasted on cardboard backing., undated (Box 6, Folder 482)
    - Dodgson, Charles "The Four Syllogisms" Ms, 1p [n.p.], November 27, 1887. 9 x 11, 1736 (Box 6, Folder 483)
    - Dodgson, Charles "To Hallie" Ms, 3pp [n.p.], November, 1868 (II 31)Inscribed to Clara Cunnynghame 6 x 7.75, 1737 (Box 6, Folder 484)
    - Dodgson, Charles "The Hunting of the Snark" Ms, 1p [n.p.], February 17, 1889 (XIX 523)Holograph draft of advertisement text. 3.25 x 7, 1741 (Box 6, Folder 485)
    - Dodgson, Charles "I sent off your promised fountain pen... " Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (IV 83) Text fragment. 1.75 x 4.5, undated; 1742 (Box 6, Folder 486)
    - Dodgson, Charles "La Guida di Bragia" Ms, 14 leaves bound in paper wrapper [n.p.], [n.d.] With correspondence and a typed copy of the play. 8.5 x 14, undated; 1745 (Box 6, Folder 487)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Let AB, CD be such Lines " Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (X 152) Mathematical notes. 11 x 9, undated; 1773 (Box 6, Folder 488)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Logic Analytical" Ms illus, 1pp [n.p.], November 21-22, 1894 (IV 83) Mathematical and/or logical diagram. Christ Church Junior Common Room account form on verso. 10.25 x 8.25, 1776 (Box 6, Folder 489)
    - Dodgson, Charles "A master of a man"s parent is that man"s superior " Ms, 1p [n.p.], March 5, 1897 (XIX 563) Originally written to Louisa Dodgson. Logic problem. 4.25 x 7, 1779 (Box 6, Folder 490)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Miss M. Cunnynghame, Debtor to Mr. C.L. Dodgson" Mss, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (II 33) A mock bill. 5.5 x 8, undated; 1780 (Box 6, Folder 491)
    - Dodgson, Charles "My first"s a drink resembling wine " Ms, 1p [n.p.], February 23, 1880 (III 42)Acrostic originally sent to Alexandra Kitchin 4.75 x 7, 1783 (Box 6, Folder 492)
    - Dodgson, Charles "My first has no beard... " Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (III 42)Acrostic originally sent to Alexandra Kitchin. 5 x 8, undated; 1784 (Box 6, Folder 493)
    - Dodgson, Charles "My first turns cows to solitary birds... " Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (III 41)Acrostic originally sent to Alexandra Kitchin. 8 x 6, undated; 1785 (Box 6, Folder 494)
    - Dodgson, Charles "My first we call here when her belt is on... " Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (IV 83) Cartoons removed to picture file. Pencil on fragment of paper. 2.5 x 4, undated; 1786 (Box 6, Folder 495)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Name, Information required" Ms, 2pp [n.p.], March 17, 1887 (346) Cast list for Saville-Clark play. 11.25 x 9, 1787 (Box 6, Folder 496)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Nella"s song" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (XIX 474a) Originally written for [Menella Wilcox] On cardboard backing. 7 x 4.5, undated; 1790 (Box 6, Folder 497)
    - Dodgson, Charles "No, no! I cannot write a line,... " Ms, 1pp [n.p.], April 10, 1871 (II 32) Verses originally written for Margaret Cunnynghame. Poem in hand not Dodgson"s on verso.. 7 x 6.75, 1793 (Box 6, Folder 498)
    - Dodgson, Charles "N.S. Began Sep. 14/1752" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], March 3, 1887 (X 144). 7 x 9, 1796 (Box 6, Folder 499)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Questions III" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] 9 x 5.75, undated; 1797 (Box 6, Folder 500)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Questions IV" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.]. 5 x 8, undated; 1798 (Box 6, Folder 501)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Symbols for properties for a pair of Lines" Ms, 1p [n.p.], April 2, 1878. 11 x 9, 1799 (Box 6, Folder 502)
    - Dodgson, Charles "There are certain conditions... " Ms, 1p [n.p.], March 23, 1893 (X 137) 8.75 x 6, 1800 (Box 6, Folder 503)
    - [Digital image with no corresponding folder], undated; 1457 (Box 6, Folder ID: 503.1)
    - Dodgson, Charles "There is this difference" Ms, 2pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (XIX 449) 8 x 12.5, undated; 1801 (Box 6, Folder 504)
    - Dodgson, Charles ""Tis the Voice of the Lobster" Ms, 1p [n.p.], October 31, 1886 (343) 9 x 7, 1806 (Box 6, Folder 505)
    - Dodgson, Charles ""Tis the Voice of the Lobster" Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (342) [--551 in DB?--]. 4.5 x 7, undated; 1807 (Box 6, Folder 506)
    - Dodgson, Charles ""Tis the Voice of the Lobster" Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (342) [--551 in DB?--]., undated; 2246 (Box 6, Folder 506)
    - Dodgson, Charles Useful and Instructive Poetry Ms, illus, 42 leaves bound in boards [Croft], 1845., 1811 (Box 6, Folder ID: 506.1)
    - Dodgson, Charles "To Dine if I come in a queer way" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], October 31, 1886 (551) Sent to Edith Lucy. 4.25 x 9, 1808 (Box 6, Folder 507)
    - Dodgson, Charles "What Tottles Meant" Ms, 4pp [n.p.], [n.d.] 9 x 5.5, undated; 1890 (Box 6, Folder 508)
    - Dodgson, Charles [Word Game] Ms, 2pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (II 30) Sent to Margaret Cunnynghame. 4.5 x 7, undated; 1895 (Box 6, Folder 509)
    - Dodgson, Charles [Word Game] Ms, 2pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (II 36) Sent to Margaret Cunnynghame. 1.5 x 3.5, undated; 1899 (Box 6, Folder 510)
  - Subseries 2B: Corrected Proofs
    - Dodgson, Charles Curiosissima Curatoria Ms corrected proof sheets 4 folded signatures, dated and numbered [n.p.], August 10. 1892 4 folded signatures. Signature A is numbered 79366, B & C 79109, and D 79276. 7.5 x 5, undated; 1902 (Box 6, Folder 511)
  - Subseries 2C: Manuscripts by others.
    - Lord Simon [Memoir of Charles Dodgson] Ts, 12pp [n.p.], [n.d.] Document contains both typescript and holograph pages., undated (Box 6, Folder 512)
    - Waterhouse, Mrs. A.T. [Memoir of Charles Dodgson] Ms, 7pp [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated (Box 6, Folder 512)
    - Rowell, Mrs. H.L. [Memoir of Charles Dodgson] Ms, 6pp [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated (Box 6, Folder 512)
    - Davies, Mrs. Arthur [Memoir of Charles Dodgson] Ts, 3pp [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated (Box 6, Folder 512)
- Series 3: Drawings
  - Subseries 3A: Drawings by Charles L. Dodgson
    - Dodgson, Charles "Copied from Wilkinson"s "Manners and Customs of the Ancient Egyptians" Vol II, pp. 18, 57" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.]. 5.5 x 8.75, undated; 1908 (Box 7, Folder 513)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Edith" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], September 14, 1880 (VI 107)Purple ink. 8.5 x 5.5, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 514)
    - Dodgson, Charles "For Ina" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.]. 11 x 8.5, undated; 1910 (Box 7, Folder 515)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Scene from the Burlesque of "Norma" acted at the Haymarket" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], September 14, 1880 11 x 8.5, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 516)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Sketch from the Concert Room at St. Lenards" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], April 10, 1868 (I 6) in pencil on verso. 4.5 x 2.5, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 517)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], September 14, 1880 Classical Scene. Three figures, two dogs. 7.25 x 4.75, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 518)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawings, 2pp, pen and ink [n.p.], October 8, 1875 (IV 83) Cartoons. Purple ink. Done for Gertrude Chataway.. 8.75 x 7, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 519)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled [n.p.], [n.d.] Man with Axe. 7 x 4.5, undated; 1919 (Box 7, Folder 520)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] (I 1) Russian Drawings. Multiple heads and Russian annotations. Holograph on verso.. 7.25 x 4.5, undated; 1920 (Box 7, Folder 521)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] Russian Drawings. Four figures and Russian annotation. 2.5 x 4.5, undated; 1923 (Box 7, Folder 522)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [Christ Church, Oxford], [Jan 30, 1868] Self Portrait of Dodgson Lecturing. See Margaret Cunnynghame correspondence. 558 in blue and 671 on verso. 4 x 2.5, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 523)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] [Tweedle Dee and Tweedle Dum] 7 x 4.5, undated; 1925 (Box 7, Folder 524)
  - Subseries 3B: Drawings by others.
    - Furniss, Harry "Alice getting smaller.." Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 525)
    - Furniss, Harry "Alice growing.." Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 526)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Baby Kind" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908] Possibly a proof Sylvie and Bruno Concluded., undated (Box 7, Folder 527)
    - Furniss, Harry "Down, down, down" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 528)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Gryphon and the Mock Turtle Dance" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 529)
    - Furniss, Harry "If you Please Sir" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 530)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Knave was standing between them.." Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 531)
    - Furniss, Harry "Lewis Carroll at the Play". Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] Figures and "by H. Furniss" on verso., undated (Box 7, Folder 532)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Mad Hatter"s Song" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 533)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Mad Tea Party" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 534)
    - Furniss, Harry "The March Hare took the Watch and Dipped it Into a Cup of Tea" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 535)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Mock Turtle"s Song" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 536)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Pool of Tears" Drawing [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 537)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Queen of Hearts" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 538)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Queer Cocktail Party", depicts the mouse"s tale Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 539)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Trial Scene" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 540)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Whole Pack Rose in the Air" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 541)
    - Furniss, Harry "The White Rabbit" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908]., undated (Box 7, Folder 541a.)
    - Furniss, Harry "What Tottles Meant" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] From Sylvie and Bruno Concluded., undated (Box 7, Folder 542)
    - Rackham, Arthur Untitled Sketchbook for Rackham"s 1907 Alice in Wonderland [n.p.] [1907]., undated (Box 7, Folder 543)
    - [Tenniel, John] Untitled Drawing [n.p.], [n.d.] Depiction of the mouse"s tale. Inscribed "From [T] with love, 1868". (Box 7, Folder 544)
    - Tenniel, John Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated (Box 7, Folder 545)
    - Tenniel, John Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated (Box 7, Folder 545)
    - Tenniel, John Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.], undated (Box 7, Folder 545)
- Series 4: Photographs
  - Subseries 4A: Photographs by Charles L. Dodgson.
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Chataway, Gertrude Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2453. [n.p.][n.d.] Legs crossed. Bathing attire. Cap. On verso "2453" and "IV 44". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1926 (Box 7, Folder 546)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] Photo of Dr.Robinson"s Class in Dr. Lee"s Museum Contemporary Photographic Print, [n.n.] [n.p.] [1858] Tipped into Fale"s copy 1 of De la Mare"s 1932 Lewis Carroll. Four men examining an animal skeleton., undated (Box 7, Folder 546.1 tipped into book)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] Photo of Wilfred Dodgson Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated in chair. Numbered II 37. Inscribed "Clara H. Cunningham/from Wilfred L. Dodgson". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1929 (Box 7, Folder 547)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Ffoulkes, [?] Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2644, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. Portrait of girl. Numbered on verso "2644", originally enclosed with letter XIX 472 to Mrs. Ffoulkes. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1932 (Box 7, Folder 548)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of[Kitchin, Alexandra] Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2012, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Sitting in chair. Numbered "2012" on verso. Also, and probably mistakenly, labeled "Liddell" on verso. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1935 (Box 7, Folder 549)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2032, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] In chair holding box. Numbered on verso "2032". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1938 (Box 7, Folder 550)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Wearing coat and hat. Numbered "2132" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1941 (Box 7, Folder 551)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print [2143], Negative Number, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Inscribed in pencil "X by Mr. Dodgson." In beach attire with shovel and bucket. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1944 (Box 7, Folder 552)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [2155] [n.p.][n.d.] In Asian kimono with fan. No number. On verso "For Herbert Kitchin /from Lewis Carroll/Sept. 10 1873". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1947 (Box 7, Folder 553)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2251, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Leaning on pillow with left arm. Numbered "2251" on verso. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1950 (Box 7, Folder 554)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra [n.p.][n.d.] Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2316, Mounted on Pasteboard In a crown and costume with leopard skin. Numbered on verso "2316". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1953 (Box 7, Folder 555)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra [n.p.][n.d.] Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2425, Mounted on Pasteboard In dress with sash, with violin. Numbered "2425" on verso. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1956 (Box 7, Folder 556)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2477, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] In dress with lace. numbered on verso "2477". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1959 (Box 7, Folder 557)
    - Dodgson, Charles Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2541, Mounted on Pasteboard Sitting on chair reading book. Numbered "2541" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1962 (Box 7, Folder 558)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2542, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] With violin standing next to chair. Numbered "2542" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1965 (Box 7, Folder 559)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.p.][n.d.] In turban with fan. Numbered "2544" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1968 (Box 7, Folder 560)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Brook Contemporary Photographic Print,Negative Number 2316, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure of child on toy horse. Numbered on verso "2316". Note that there is another Dodgson of Alexandra Kitchin with the same number. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1971 (Box 7, Folder 561)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Brook Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2318, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure of child with mustache and costume. Numbered on verso "2318".) 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1974 (Box 7, Folder 562)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, George Herbert Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2141, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. Full length figure in jacket with frog fastenings. Numbered "2141" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1977 (Box 7, Folder 563)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, George Herbert Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2142, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. 3/4 length figure in jacket with frog fastenings. Numbered in purple ink on verso in upper right corner"2134/ 2142.". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1980 (Box 7, Folder 564)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra and Dorothy Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2641, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Two girls together. Numbered "2641" on verso. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1983 (Box 7, Folder 565)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Brook and Hugh Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2336, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length. On verso numbered "2336". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1986 (Box 7, Folder 566)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Liddell, Alice, Edith and Lorina Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2463, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Sir W.B. Richmond"s painting of Liddell girls at the beach. 2463 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1989 (Box 7, Folder 567)
    - [Dodgson, Charles ] Photo of Liddon, Rev. H.P Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated, reading. Signed on verso "Miss E [T] Sewell/from the artist 4 x 2.5, undated; 1990 (Box 7, Folder 568)
    - [Dodgson, Charles ] Photo of Ruskin, John Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2309, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated in chair. Numbered "2309" Signed on verso "Miss Effie Neef /From the Artist/Nov. 11,"79. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1993 (Box 7, Folder 569)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Standen, Isabel Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 1813, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] With croquet mallet. Numbered on verso "1813" and "VIII 126". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1996 (Box 7, Folder 570)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Standen, Maud and Isabel Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 1812, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] With brick wall and foliage. Numbered "1812" and "VIII 126". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1999 (Box 7, Folder 571)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] Photo of Stevens, Enid or Winifred Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated on chair. See XII 220 in correspondence. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2002 (Box 7, Folder 572)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] Photo of Stevens, Enid or Winifred Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated on bench. On verso "W. Forshaw/Platinotype/Portraits/ Oxford/ 57 Giles". See XII 220) 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2005 (Box 7, Folder 573)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Charles Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure with croquet mallet standing before brick wall. 4 x 3, undated; 2008 (Box 8, Folder 574)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Charles Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length seated figure wearing suit with vertical stripes. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2009 (Box 8, Folder 575)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Ellen Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure dressed in kimono standing in front of cloth backdrop and brick wall. 8.25 x 6.5, undated; 2010 (Box 8, Folder 576)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 1343, Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Girl in dress leans against prop. 8x10"Numbered "1343" on verso. Not mounted on pasteboard. 10 x 7.75, undated; 2011 (Box 8, Folder 577)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number, Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Girl sits on rug in front of prop. No number. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2014 (Box 8, Folder 578)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Girl sits on rug in front of prop. No number. 6.25 x 4.75, undated; 2015 (Box 8, Folder 579)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure with head averted and eyes closed standing against brick wall. 4 x 3, undated; 2019 (Box 8, Folder 580)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Girl pares fruit with one foot up on box. 8x10. 9.75 x 7.75, undated; 2020 (Box 8, Folder 581)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure with head averted standing against door. 4 x 3, undated; 2021 (Box 8, Folder 582)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure with eyes closed leaning against a door background of door and brick wall, with head reflected in glass panel of door. 4 x 3, undated; 2022 (Box 8, Folder 583)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure seated with ends of scarf crossing on her chest 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2023 (Box 8, Folder 584)
    - Dodgson, Charles Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure in checked skirt, double puffed sleeves, and doublet with embroidered edge. 4 x 3, undated; 2024 (Box 8, Folder 585)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure of woman in flowered print dress and beribboned cap reclining in an easy chair. 8.25 x 6.25, undated; 2025 (Box 8, Folder 586)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Full side view of Terry, Kate as Andromeda with crossed arms suspended from a silken rope. 9.75 x 7.75, undated; 2026 (Box 8, Folder 587)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure in chain mail with hand clasping a sword, and with a background of a prop supported by a brick wall. 8.5 x 6.5, undated; 2027 (Box 8, Folder 588)